RG 005, Office of the Governor Records
Governor Records, Office of the
- Series 1. Executive Clerk, 1820-1985
  - Executive Journal, 1820-1985
    - T001304, 31 volumes
      - 1826 November 14-1829 June 5 (Volume Vol. 3)
      - 1829 June-1835 May 6 (Volume Vol. 4)
      - 1835 May 7-1839 June 7 (Volume Vol. 5)
      - 1839 June 11-1845 April 29 (Volume Vol. 6)
      - 1845 May 7-1850 April 29 (Volume Vol. 7)
      - 1850 May 2-1854 June 1 (Volume Vol. 8)
      - 1854 July 10-1859 March 2 (Volume Vol. 9)
      - 1859 March 10-1862 February 25 (Volume Vol. 10)
      - 1862 February 26-1863 September 25 (Volume Vol. 11)
      - 1863 September 25-1865 December 18 (Volume Vol. 12)
      - Index to Vol. 12 (Volume Index Vol.)
        Separate volume.
      - 1865 December 18-1870 July 13 (Volume Vol. 13)
      - 1870 July 13-1874 December 31 (Volume Vol. 14)
      - 1875 January 2-1878 April 30 (Volume Vol. 15)
      - 1878 May 8-1882 April 25 (Volume Vol. 16)
      - 1882 April 25-1886 April 9 (Volume Vol. 17)
      - 1886 April 9-1892 November 15 (Volume Vol. 18)
      - 1892 November 16-1896 December 18 (Volume Vol. 19)
      - 1896 December 18-1901 March 22 (Volume Vol. 20)
      - 1901 March 25-1905 April 19 (Volume Vol. 21)
      - 1905 April 19-1909 January 6 (Volume Vol. 22)
      - 1909 January 6-1912 February 13 (Volume Vol. 23)
      - 1912 February 13-1915 June 29 (Volume Vol. 24)
      - 1915 June 29-1919 January 16 (Volume Vol. 25)
      - 1919 January 16-1922 July 5 (Volume Vol. 26)
      - 1922 July 5-1926 February 3 (Volume Vol. 27)
      - 1926 February 3-1926 August 6 (Volume Vol. 28)
      - 1929 August 6-1933 April 28 (Volume Vol. 29)
      - 1933 May 1-1935 January 9 (Volume Vol. 30)
    - T001508
      - 1959-1965 (Box 1)
      - 1966-1968 July 1 (Box 2)
      - 1968 July 2-1969 February (Box 3)
      - 1968 March-August (Box 4)
      - 1969 September-1970 May (Box 5)
      - 1970 June-December (Box 6)
      - 1971 January-July 6 (Box 7)
      - 1971 July 7-December (Box 8)
      - 1972 January-August (Box 9)
      - 1972 September-1973 May (Box 10)
      - 1973 June-December (Box 11)
      - 1974 January-June (Box 12)
      - 1974 July-December (Box 13)
      - 1975 January-July (Box 14)
      - 1975 August-1976 March (Box 15)
      - 1976 April-September (Box 16)
      - 1976 October-1977 February (Box 17)
      - 1977 March-July (Box 18)
      - 1977 August-December (Box 19)
      - 1978 January-July (Box 20)
      - 1978 August-1979 February (Box 21)
      - 1979 March-July (Box 22)
      - 1979 August-November (Box 23)
      - 1979 December-1980 May (Box 24)
      - 1980 June-December (Box 25)
      - 1981 January-August (Box 26)
      - 1981 September-1982 February (Box 27)
      - 1982 March-August (Box 28)
      - 1982 September-1983 March (Box 29)
      - 1983 April-August (Box 30)
      - 1983 September-1984 February (Box 31)
      - 1984 March-October (Box 32)
      - 1985 May-August (Box 33)
  - William F. Siering, Jr. Files, 1946-1985
    - T001494
      - Appointments, 1958-1985
        - Academic Awards, Board for State, 1973-1977 (Box 1)
        - Accountancy, State Board of, 1973-1976 (Box 1)
        - Adjutant General, 1979 June 27 (Box 1)
        - Administrative Service, 1977 July 14 (Box 1)
        - Adoption Review Board, 1975-1977 (Box 1)
        - Adult Probation, Commission on, 1973-1977 (Box 1)
        - Aging, Commissioner on, 1975-1977 (Box 1)
        - Aging, Advisory Council on, 1973-1977 (Box 1)
        - Agriculture, Board of, 1973-1977 (Box 1)
        - Agriculture Experiment Station, Board of Control, 1973-1976 (Box 1)
        - Agriculture, Commissioner of, 1973-1977 (Box 1)
        - Agricultural Land, Governor's Task Force for the Preservation of, 1974 April-June (Box 1)
        - Alcohol and Drug Abuse Council, State, 1977 (Box 1)
        - Alcohol Advisory Council, Connecticut State, 1972-1977 July; 2 folders (Box 1)
        - American and Francophone Cultural Commission, 1974-1980 (Box 1)
        - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission of Connecticut, 1971-1974 (Box 1)
        - American School for the Deaf, Board of Directors, 1971-1975 (Box 1)
        - Appalachian National Scenic Trail Advisory Council, 1975 May 2 (Box 1)
        - Apprenticeship Council, Connecticut State, 1971-1977 (Box 1)
        - Appropriations, Joint Standing Committee on, 1973-1975 (Box 1)
        - Arborist Examining Board, Connecticut, 1976 November 18 (Box 1)
        - Architectural Registration Board, 1975-1977 (Box 1)
        - Arts, Commission on the, 1972-1977 (Box 1)
        - Asbestos, Task Force to study the Public Health Hazards of, 1980 June 20 (Box 1)
        - Atlantic States Marine Fisheries Commission, 1972-1975 (Box 1)
        - Attorney General, 1976 November 14 (Box 1)
        - Auditors, State, 1976 June 3 (Box 1)
        - Banking Commissioner, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
        - Banking, Advisory Council on, 1972-1975 (Box 2)
        - Banking Law and Related Statutes, Advisory Committee to study, 1976 May-June (Box 2)
        - Bi-State Long Island Sound Marine Resources Committee, 1973 July (Box 2)
        - Blind persons, Committee for the purchase of products and services of, 1977 March 16 (Box 2)
        - Blind, Board of Education and Services for the, 1971-1977 (Box 2)
        - Boiler Safety Board, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
        - Cable Telecommunications, Commission on the Educational and Information uses of, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
        - Capitol Preservation and Restoration, State Commission on, 1973-1977 (Box 2)
        - Career Education Task Force, 1977 May 3 (Box 2)
        - Center for Urban and Economic Studies at the University of Connecticut, 1973-1977 (Box 2)
        - Chemists, State, 1973-1976 (Box 2)
        - Child Day Care, Director of, 1975 October 21 (Box 2)
        - Child Day Care Council, 1973-1977 (Box 2)
        - Children and Youth Services, State Advisory Council on, 1972-1980 (Box 2)
        - Children and Youth Services, Commissioner of, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
        - Children Commission to further study and report on the transfer of, 1974-1976 (Box 2)
        - Children, Interstate Compact on the Placement of, 1967 (Box 2)
        - Children's Services, Commission on, 1976 June-August (Box 2)
        - Chiropractic, State Board of Examiners, 1974-1977 (Box 2)
        - Civil Defense Advisory Council, 1959 (Box 2)
        - Civil Preparedness Advisory Council, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
        - Civil Preparedness Director, 1975 May 7 (Box 2)
        - Claims, Commission on, 1973-1975 (Box 2)
        - Claims Commissioner, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
        - Coast Guard, 1977 May 17-23 (Box 2)
        - Code of Ethics Committee, 1975 January (Box 2)
        - Commerce, Commissioner of, 1973-1975 (Box 2)
        - Commissioners, 1967-1975 (Box 2)
        - Committee of Concern for Connecticut Jobs, 1972-1977 (Box 2)
        - Community Affairs, Advisory Council on, 1972-1977 (Box 2)
        - Community Affairs, Commissioner of, 1971-1976 (Box 2)
        - Community Colleges, Board of trusties of the, 1974 September 30 (Box 2)
        - Compensation Commission, 1971-1980 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut Capitol Center Commission, 1971-1977 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut Comprehensive Health Planning Council, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut Development Authority, 1971-1977 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut Education Council, 1972-1977 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut Justice Commission, 1971-1979; 2 folders (Box 3)
        - Connecticut Product Development Corporation, 1972-1977 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut Public Transportation Authority, 1975-1977 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut Public Transportation Authority, 1975-1977 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut Research Commission, 1967-1971 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut Resources Recovery Authority, 1973-1977 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut River Dredging Committee, 1972 October 5 (Box 3)
        - Connecticut River Valley Flood Control Commission, 1973-1977 (Box 3)
        - Consumers Advisory Council, 1973-1977 (Box 3)
        - Consumer Counsel, 1977 September-November (Box 3)
        - Consumer Protection, Commissioner of, 1975 (Box 3)
        - Convention and Visitors Convention, 1974-1980 (Box 3)
        - Correction, Commissioner of, 1975 January 13 (Box 3)
        - Correction, Council of, 1972-1977 (Box 3)
        - Correction Industries Advisory Commission, 1973-1977 (Box 3)
        - Criminal Administration, Connecticut Planning Committee on, 1971-1975 (Box 3)
        - Deaf and Hearing Impaired, Commission on the, 1972-1977; 2 folders (Box 4)
        - Deeds, Commissioner of, 1971-1979 (Box 4)
        - Demolition, State Commission on, 1973-1977 (Box 4)
        - Dental Commissioners, 1973-1980 (Box 4)
        - Development Disabilities Services and Facilities Construction Act, State Planning and, 1970-1977; 2 folders (Box 4)
        - Developmentally Disabled Assistance and Bill of Rights Act of 1975, 1976; 2 folders (Box 4)
        - Drug Advisory Council, 1969-1976 (Box 4)
        - Drug Council Executive Director, 1973-1975 (Box 4)
        - Eastern Connecticut Rural and Industrial Areas Preservation Commission, 1975 July-September (Box 4)
        - Eastern Regional Committees, 1975 February 18 (Box 4)
        - Economic Advisors, Council of, 1972-1975 (Box 4)
        - Education, State Board of, 1973-1980 (Box 4)
        - Education, State Department of: Arbitration Panel, 1974-1976 (Box 4)
        - Education Commission of the States, 1971-1977 (Box 4)
        - Education Statutes, Commission to Revise and Recodify the, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
        - Elected State Officials and Judges, Commission on Compensation for, 1975 July-October (Box 4)
        - Election Laws, Governor's Commission to Rewrite Connecticut's, 1969-1973 (Box 4)
        - Elections Commission, State, 1974-1980 (Box 4)
        - Electrical Work Examining Board, 1973-1977 (Box 5)
        - Elevator Installation, Repair and Maintenance Work Examining Board, 1975-1977 (Box 5)
        - Embalmers and Funeral Directors, Board of Examiners of, 1972-1980 (Box 5)
        - Emergency Medical Services, Connecticut Advisory Committee on, 1974 May-1977; 3 folders (Box 5)
        - Emergency Price Control, State Committee, 1962-1970 (Box 5)
        - Emergency Rationing, State Committee on, 1962 (Box 5)
        - Emergency Rent Control, State Committee on, 1962-1971 (Box 5)
        - Employment, Governor's Strike Force for Full, 1971 November-December (Box 5)
        - Employment Security Advisory Council, 1973-1977 (Box 5)
        - Employment Security, Board of Review, 1974-1977 (Box 5)
        - Energy Advisory Board, Connecticut, 1974-1977 (Box 5)
        - Energy Emergency Agency, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
        - Engineers and Land Surveyors, Board of Registration for, 1967-1977 (Box 5)
        - Environmental Protection and Economic Development, Commission on, 1975-1977 (Box 5)
        - Environmental Protection, Commissioner of, 1972-1977 (Box 5)
        - Environmental Quality, Council on, 1971-1977 (Box 5)
        - Epilepsy and Other Neurological Conditions, Commission to study the Problems, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
        - Equal Employment Opportunity, Connecticut Council for, 1971 June-July (Box 5)
        - Equine Advisory Council, Connecticut, 1973-1977 (Box 5)
        - Ethics Commission, State, 1977-1980 (Box 5)
        - Executive Nominations, Committee on, 1973-1977 (Box 5)
        - Fairfield Hills Hospital, Board of Trustees of the, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
        - Farmington River Valley Flood Control Commission, 1972-1975 (Box 6)
        - Finance and Control, Commissioner of, 1974-1977 (Box 6)
        - Finance Advisory Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 6)
        - Fire Code Standards Committee, 1975-1980 (Box 6)
        - Fire Fighting personnel and Education, Commission of, 1973-1975 (Box 6)
        - Fire Prevention and Control, Commission on, 1975-1980 (Box 6)
        - Firearms, Board of Permit Examiners, 1967-1976 (Box 6)
        - Fishery, Regional management Council, 1976-1977 (Box 6)
        - Fitness, Governor's Committee on, 1972-1980 (Box 6)
        - Five Mile River Commission, 1969-1977 (Box 6)
        - Forfeited Rights, Commission on, 1973 June-August (Box 6)
        - Freedom of Information Commission, 1975-1977 (Box 6)
        - Gas Pricing, Committee to Investigate, 1973 March (Box 6)
        - Goodspeed Opera House, 1972-1976 (Box 6)
        - Government Administration and Policy, Joint Legislative Committee on, 1973 February 13 (Box 6)
        - Governor's Staff, 1973-1975 (Box 6)
        - Greater Hartford Flood Commission, 1955-1977 (Box 6)
        - Handicapped, Board of Protection and Advocacy for the, 1977 August-September (Box 6)
        - Handicapped, Governor's Committee on Employment of the, 1970-1976 (Box 6)
        - Harbor Masters, 1968-1980; 5 folders (Box 7)
        - Harbor masters, Deputy, 1971-1977 (Box 7)
        - Hartford Hospital, Directors of, 1971-1980 (Box 7)
        - Hazardous Waste Interim Study Committee, 1980 June (Box 7)
        - Health and Educational Facilities Authority, State of Connecticut, 1971-1977 (Box 7)
        - Health and Safety Codes, Inter-Agency Committee on, 1971-1974 (Box 7)
        - Health Bureau, State, 1976 August 27 (Box 7)
        - Health, Commissioner of, 1971-1976 (Box 7)
        - Health Coordinating Council, Statewide, 1975-1980 (Box 7)
        - Health Maintenance Organizations, Commission on, 1975-1977 (Box 7)
        - Health Planning and Resources Development Act, 1975 January-May (Box 7)
        - Health Planning, Advisory Council for Comprehensive, 1973-1974 (Box 7)
        - Health Planning Council, Connecticut Comprehensive, 1970-1973 (Box 7)
        - Health Systems Agency Review Team, 1973 January 23 (Box 7)
        - Hear Town Grievances, Committee to, 1973-1977 (Box 7)
        - Hearing Aids, Advisory Council on, 1972-1976 (Box 7)
        - Hearing Aid Dealers Licensure, Advisory Council on, 1974-1975 (Box 7)
        - Heating, Piping and Cooling Work Examining Board, 1968-1977 (Box 7)
        - High Meadows, Board of Trustees of, 1955-1972 (Box 7)
        - High Unemployment in the State, Commission on, 1975-1977 (Box 7)
        - Higher Education, Commission for, 1969-1972; 2 folders (Box 8)
        - Higher Education, Connecticut Board of, 1977 July-August (Box 8)
        - Higher Education, Connecticut Commission on Aid to, 1965-1972 (Box 8)
        - Higher Education Assistance Corporation, Connecticut, 1959-1961 (Box 8)
        - Higher Education Assistance Corporation, Connecticut, 1962-1970 (Box 8)
        - Higher Education, New England Board of, 1955-1977 (Box 8)
        - Highway Safety, Inter-Agency Committee on, 1972-1975 (Box 8)
        - Historic Assets in Connecticut, Committee for the Restoration of, 1977 July 6 (Box 8)
        - Historic Preservation, Connecticut Trust for, 1975-1977 (Box 8)
        - Historical Commission, Connecticut, 1968-1980; 2 folders (Box 8)
        - Historical Records Advisory Board, 1976-1977 (Box 8)
        - Homeopathic Medical examining Board, Connecticut, 1970-1977 (Box 8)
        - Hospitals and Health Care, Commission on, 1973-1977; 2 folders (Box 8)
        - Hospitals, Council on, 1969-1972 (Box 8)
        - Housing, Commissioner of, 1979-1980 (Box 8)
        - Housing Court or Housing Division of the Court of Common Pleas, Commission to study the Creation of a, 1976 June-July (Box 8)
        - Housing Finance Authority, Connecticut, 1972-1980 (Box 8)
        - Housing Matters, Council for, 1980 September 17 (Box 8)
        - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
        - Human Rights and Opportunities, Executive Committee on, 1971-1975 (Box 9)
        - Human Rights and Opportunities, Commission on, Hearing Examiners for the, 1968-1977 (Box 9)
        - Human Services, Council on, 1973-1976 (Box 9)
        - Humane Society, Connecticut: Prosecuting Officers of the, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
        - Humanities Council, Connecticut, 1976-1977 (Box 9)
        - Hypertrichologists, Board of Examiners of, 1973-1977 (Box 9)
        - Income Maintenance, Commissioner of, 1978 December 27 (Box 9)
        - Indian Affairs Council, 1973-1980 (Box 9)
        - Industrial Building Commission, 1972 January-April (Box 9)
        - Industrial Modernization, Advisory Committee on, 1972-1973 (Box 9)
        - Industrial Safety Commission, 1972 October 5 (Box 9)
        - Insurance Commissioner, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
        - Insurance Purchasing Board, State, 1958-1980; 2 folder (Box 9)
        - Inter-Department Traffic Coordinating Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
        - Intergovernmental Cooperation, Governor's Committee on, 1973-1977 (Box 9)
        - Internal Communications, Director of, 1973 July 10 (Box 9)
        - Interstate Sanitation Commission, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
        - Interstate Water Compact Commission, Connecticut, 1973-1977 (Box 9)
        - Investment Advisory Council, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
        - Investment Advisory Council, 1975-1980 (Box 9)
        - Investment Committee, 1971 April 29 (Box 9)
        - Italian Appointees, 1972 May 11, undated (Box 9)
        - Job Innovation and Development, Commission on, 1975-1977 (Box 9)
        - Judicial Council, 1975-1980 (Box 9)
        - Judicial Review Council, 1973-1975 (Box 9)
        - Judge Advocate, State, 1967-1973 (Box 9)
        - Judges, General, 1960-1977 (Box 9)
        - Judges, Circuit Court, 1967-1972 (Box 9)
        - Judges, Common Pleas Court, 1967-1977 (Box 9)
        - Judges, Juvenile Court, 1965-1976 (Box 9)
        - Judges, Superior Court, 1965-1979 (Box 9)
        - Judges, Superior Court, 1968-1974 (Box 9)
        - Kidney Foundation of Connecticut, 1975-1977 (Box 10)
        - Labor Commissioner, 1975-1976 (Box 10)
        - Labor Relations, State Board of, 1971-1977 (Box 10)
        - Landscape Architecture, State Board of, 1975-1977 (Box 10)
        - Law Library Advisory Committee, 1976 June-October (Box 10)
        - Law Revision Commission, Connecticut, 1976-1980 (Box 10)
        - Legal Services Advisory Council, 1974-1977 (Box 10)
        - Legislative Audit Review Committee, 1937-1977 (Box 10)
        - Legislative Ethics Committee, Joint, 1972-1977 (Box 10)
        - Legislative management, Joint Committee on, 1973-1977 (Box 10)
        - Legislative Program review Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 10)
        - Legislative Regulations Review Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 10)
        - Legislative Staff Internships, Committee for, 1973-1977 (Box 10)
        - Liquor Control Commission, 1971-1977 (Box 10)
        - Local Governments in Connecticut, Commission on, 1980 June 23 (Box 10)
        - Manpower Services Council, Connecticut State, 1973-1976; 3 folders (Box 10)
        - Mansfield Training School, 1974-1976 (Box 10)
        - Marketing Authority, Connecticut, 1971-1977 (Box 10)
        - Mediation and Arbitration, State Board of, 1970-1972; 2 folders (Box 10)
        - Medical Assistance Program, Task Force to Study Connecticut's, 1975 July 11 (Box 11)
        - Medical - Dental School, Commission to Select a Site for, 1962-1966 (Box 11)
        - Medical Examining Board, Connecticut, 1957-1980; 3 folders (Box 11)
        - Medical Health Insurance Policies Regarding the Coverage for Costs of Mental Illness, Commission to Study, 1969 July-August (Box 11)
        - Medicolegal Investigations, Committee on, 1969-1980 (Box 11)
        - Mental Health, Commissioner of, 1957-1976 (Box 11)
        - Mental Health, Board of, 1963-1977 (Box 11)
        - Mental Retardation, Council on, 1966-1980 (Box 11)
        - Mentally Deficient, Compact Administrator for the, 1971-1975 (Box 11)
        - Mentally Ill, Compact Administrator for the, 1971-1976 (Box 11)
        - Metric Coordinating Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 11)
        - Metropolitan District Commission, 1964-1976 (Box 11)
        - Military, Governor's Staff, 1955-1976; 5 folders (Box 11)
        - Milk Regulation Board, 1967-1977 (Box 12)
        - Mobile Homes, Advisory Committee on, 1972-1977 (Box 12)
        - Mortgage Authority, Connecticut, 1970-1977 (Box 12)
        - Motor Vehicle Emission Inspection Agreements, Committee on, 1980 June 20 (Box 12)
        - Motor Vehicles, Commissioner of, 1959-1977 (Box 12)
        - Municipal Police Training Council, 1965-1980 (Box 12)
        - Mystic Oral School, Board of trustees of the, 1968-1977 (Box 12)
        - Narcotics Advisory Council, 1961-1963 (Box 12)
        - National Consumer Information Center, Advisory Council of the, 1973 December 18 (Box 12)
        - National Guard, Connecticut, 1974 August 1 (Box 12)
        - National Area Preserves Advisory Committee, 1969-1977 (Box 12)
        - Natureopathic Examiners, State Board of, 1971-1977 (Box 12)
        - Naugatuck Valley Loan Fund Advisory Committee, 1980 August 29 (Box 12)
        - Naugatuck Valley River Control Commission, 1955-1968 (Box 12)
        - Naval Militia, Connecticut, 1973-1975 (Box 12)
        - Negro Appointees, 1972 February 7 (Box 12)
        - New Britain Memorial Hospital, Board of Directors of the, 1969-1980 (Box 12)
        - New England Association of Schools and Colleges, 1973-1975 (Box 12)
        - New England College of Optometry, 1976-1977 (Box 12)
        - New England College of Veterinary Medicine, 1975 August-December (Box 12)
        - New England Interstate Water Pollution Control Commission, 1971-1977 (Box 12)
        - New England Program for Teacher Education, 1971 March-November (Box 12)
        - New England regional Commission, 1971-1975 (Box 12)
        - New England River Basins Commission, 1967-1977 (Box 12)
        - New Haven Harbor, Board of Harbor Commissioners for, 1972-1977 (Box 12)
        - New London Country Courthouse, 1968-1971 (Box 12)
        - New Uses for Old Buildings Committee, 1972 December (Box 12)
        - Newington Children's Hospital, Board of Directors of the, 1971-1974 (Box 12)
        - No-Fault Insurance Study Committee, 1971 July-August (Box 12)
        - Noah Webster Foundation, The, 1972 May-September (Box 12)
        - Noise Abatement Policy Committee, 1980 November 26 (Box 12)
        - Noncollege-bound students, Commission to study means of providing greater opportunities for, 1969 August-September (Box 12)
        - Nonpublic School Secular Education, Commission to study Public Assistance to, 1969 April-1969 December; 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Nonpublic School Secular Education, Advisory Council on, 1969-1972 (Box 12)
        - Northeastern Forest Fire Protect Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
        - Northeastern Resources Commission, 1974 August (Box 12)
        - Norwich Hospital, Board of Trustees of the, 1971 February-July (Box 12)
        - Nuclear Power Evaluation Council, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
        - Nursing, Connecticut State Board of Examiners, 1969-1980 (Box 13)
        - Nursing Home Administrators, Board for the Licensure of, 1970-1977; 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Nursing Homes, Blue Ribbon Committee to Investigate, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
        - Occupational Licensing, State Boards for, 1965-1973 (Box 13)
        - Occupational Safety and Health Review Commission, 1973-1977; 2 folders (Box 13)
        - Opticians, Commission on, 1971-1980 (Box 13)
        - Optometry, Connecticut State Board of Examiners in, 1973-1977 (Box 13)
        - Organized Crime Prevention and Control, Advisory Committee on, 1973-1976 (Box 13)
        - Osteopathic Examining Board, 1971-1977 (Box 13)
        - Outstanding Older Americans, Selection Committee for, undated (Box 13)
        - Pardons, Board of, 1964-1977; 2 folders (Box 14)
        - Parole, Board of, 1967-1980; 3 folders (Box 14)
        - Parole Evaluation and the Commission to Study Alternative Methods of Sentencing Criminals, Commission on, 1977 June 6 (Box 14)